<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.audiooffsetmanagerevolved" version="1.0.0~beta4" name="AOM Evolved" provider-name="matthane">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="script.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <source>https://github.com/matthane/script.audiooffsetmanager</source>
        <news>v1.0.0~beta4 (2026-07-16)
- Unlearned stream profiles now reset the audio offset to 0 once the addon has acted, instead of letting a previous stream's offset stick
- "Offset not saved" notification when an unstored manual adjustment is discarded by that reset
- The manage-offsets view returns to the addon settings when closed and gains a "Back to settings" row

v1.0.0~beta3 (2026-07-15)
- Log lines now use the AOMe_ prefix so Evolved is distinguishable from classic AOM in a shared kodi.log

v1.0.0~beta2 (2026-07-15)
- Fix toast rendering: the saved/applied line is now the notification title (no more scrolling/truncated single line)
- Toasts omit the frame rate while per-refresh-rate offsets are disabled (the value is stored for all rates)
- Display name for TrueHD Atmos

v1.0.0~beta1 (2026-07-15)
- First beta of AOM Evolved (local test build; never published)
- Learn loop: manual offset adjustments are remembered per stream profile and re-applied automatically
- Sparse JSON offset store with per-refresh-rate toggle, verbatim format acceptance
- Management view (settings button): inspect and remove learned offsets
- One-time warning when the classic Audio Offset Manager is also enabled
        </news>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Fix lipsync once — Evolved remembers it per stream profile</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Adjust Kodi's audio offset during playback the way you always have. AOM Evolved remembers the value for that stream's HDR type, audio format, and refresh rate, then re-applies it automatically on every matching playback. Includes seek-back after adjustments, playback notifications, and a management view of everything it has learned.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-1.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-2.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-3.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
