<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.audiooffsetmanager.evolved" version="1.0.0~beta11" name="Audio Offset Manager: Evolved" provider-name="matthane">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="script.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <source>https://github.com/matthane/script.audiooffsetmanager</source>
        <news>v1.0.0~beta11 (2026-07-17)
- Stored offsets list shows a frame rate only when Per-frame-rate offsets is on; entries saved for a specific rate keep their rate and stay marked inactive while it is off
- Inactive entries are dimmed, and HDR type names are bold in the group list
- Simpler settings layout: the Offsets and Advanced categories no longer use group headers

v1.0.0~beta10 (2026-07-17)
- New addon ID, icon, and fanart. Install this version fresh; to keep learned offsets, copy offsets.json from the old addon_data folder to the new one
- Learning and applying are now separate toggles: Learn audio offsets stores your adjustments, Apply audio offsets replays stored ones. Both off matches the old pause
- The four seek-back toggles merged into one Seek back after selection with a shared seconds slider
- Offset change seek-back now fires when an adjustment settles, not only when it is saved
- Manage view groups whenever two or more HDR types are stored, each group can be cleared on its own, and HDR10+ is labeled correctly
        </news>
        <!-- news is schema-capped at 1500 characters (addon-checker
             enforces it): keep only the last couple of versions here;
             earlier changelogs live in the git history. -->
        <summary lang="en_GB">Fix lipsync once and Evolved remembers it per stream profile</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Adjust Kodi's audio offset during playback the way you always have. Audio Offset Manager: Evolved remembers the value for that stream's HDR type, audio format, and frame rate, then re-applies it automatically on every matching playback. Includes seek-back after adjustments, playback notifications, and a management view of everything it has learned.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-1.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-2.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-3.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
